Guide to the Consolidation Coal Company Records, 1854-1971 AIS.2011.03
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Secretary's Contract Files, VI.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and Charles McDaniel et ux, November 2, 1925; 2661.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and Harry McCorkle, Jr. et ux, November 6, 1925; 2662.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and Paul Zelinski, November 9, 1925; 2663.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and Anna Kniska, November 5, 1925; 2665.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and L.O. McKinney, July 31, 1925; 2668.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and John Tomsick, December 17, 1925; 2670.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and Joseph Mavrich, December 17, 1925; 2671.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and T. Alfreds, December 17, 1925; 2681.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and The Williams Unit System, Inc., December 29, 1925; 2682.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and Carrie Liggins, February 9, 1926; 2685.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and Pete Heirendt et ux, February 9, 1926; 2686.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and Harry J. Lyons et ux., March 2, 1926; 2689.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and Harvey Bush et ux, March 2, 1926; 2690.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and Lottie Coal Co., February 10, 1926-October 27, 1928; 2691.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and Paul Grmusha, March 24, 1926; 2695.
  - Riverview Plan of Lots, February 24, 1926; 2696.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and T. J. Clark, L. W. King and F. A. Howe, January 1, 1926; 2700.
  - The Dravo Contracting Company and Pittsburgh Coal Company, July 30, 1929; 2704.
  - John W. Boileau, January 7, 1901; 2707.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and Estie J. Heines et al, January 22-March 19, 1926; 2708.
  - Borough of Centerville, Washington County, April 6, 1926; 2710.
  - Ruth C. Wood (agent for D. H. Courtney et al), March 26, 1926; 2711.
  - Nathan Berman and R. J. Brennan, April 1, 1926; 2718.
  - 21 West Street Corporation and Pittsburgh Coal Co. Inc., February 6, 1923; 2723.
  - Number One Broadway Corporation and Robin E. Frazer, April 20, 1926; 2723.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and Mike Duda, Sr. et ux, May 19, 1926; 2724.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and George Dobric, June 10, 1926; 2730.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co., June 14, 1926-December 24, 1927; 2731.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and Robert O. Keeney, June 1, 1926; 2732.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and the Hocking Valley Railway Co., June 8, 1926; 2735.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and James Figola, July 1, 1926; 2741.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and Andrew Blackburn et ux., July 26, 1926; 2743.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and John Galuska, August 14, 1926; 2745.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and Monessen Coal & Coke Co., August 16, 1926-May 10, 1927; 2747. (Box 68)
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and McPherson Brothers, August 30, 1926-September 17, 1927; 2756.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and Charles O. Downer, August 23, 1926; 2757.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and H. A. McDermott and John Balas, September 7, 1926; 2758.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and Maxwell Coal Co., August 6, 1926; 2760.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and John Tomsick, September 23, 1926; 2761.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and Deane & Lowes, August 26, 1926; 2762.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and Thomas Staff et ux., August 31, 1926; 2765.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co., Inc. and Albert Muroski, June 1, 1933; 2771.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and John W. Semola et ux, October 11, 1926; 2774.
  - A. G. Rotherg and Pittsburgh Coal Co., September 18, 1926; 2775.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and Monongahela Clay Manufacturing Co., October 15, 1926; 2776.
  - The Monongahela River Consolidated Coal & Coke Co. and Lucyville Ferry Co., January 21, 1903; 2785.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and Lorenzo Checca, November 17, 1926; 2793.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and Earl R. Russell, October 21, 1926; 2796.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and S. M. Downer, December 1, 1926; 2797.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and Charles A. Wright et ux, Gallation Coal Co., November 15, 1926; 2798.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and Robert W. Thomas et ux, December 1, 1926; 2800.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and William Derrett, December 1, 1926; 2801.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and James S. Murray, October 21, 1926; 2804.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and John Young, Sr., December 7, 1926; 2805.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and J. F. Englers, May 26, 1925; 2807.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and D. Benton, November 23, 1926; 2808.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and (F. O. Dewar) Fayette-Tremont Coal Co., November 4, 1926; 2811.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and C. R. Buchheit, J. J. Gerlach, Jr. and R. L. Taylor, January 25, 1927-August 31, 1934; 2816.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and William K. Brown and Robert K. Brown, December 23, 1926; 2817.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and Bridgeville Coal Co. (William F. Lindley), January 19, 1927; 2819.
  - C. Bonopart and Pittsburgh Coal Co., March 23, 1927; 2821.
  - S. J. Harry Co. and Pittsburgh Coal Co., July 22, 1927; 2822.
  - A. G. Rothey and Pittsburgh Coal Co., May 16-October 3, 1927; 2826.
  - A. G. Rothey, July 13-August 15, 1927; 2827.
  - A. Nefos and Pittsburgh Coal Co., April 19, 1927-October 17, 1930; 2828.
  - Fairchance Lumber Co. and Pittsburgh Coal Co., February 17, 1927-November 25, 1927; 2829 A-G.
  - Fairchance Lumber Co. and Pittsburgh Coal Co., November 25, 1927-January 14, 1928; 2829 H-K.
  - Fairchance Lumber Co. and Pittsburgh Coal Co. (Blueprint pulled to map case 1/7/7-8), February 23, 1928-December 7, 1928; 2829 L-O.
  - Fairchance Lumber Co. and Pittsburgh Coal Co., January 31, 1929-June 28, 1929; 2829 P-R.
  - William Semple et al and Pittsburgh Coal Co., April 26, 1928; 2831. (Box 69)
  - The Milwaukee-Western Steamship Co., June 24, 1921-December 31, 1932; 2838. (Oversize 129)
  - The Mentor Transit Co., August 26, 1919-December 27, 1938; 2839.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and D. Berton, August 10, 1927-August 1, 1935; 2844. (Box 69)
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and Standard Natural Gas Co., August 12, 1931; 2857.
  - Robert F. Allen, March 30, 1927; 2858.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and Allen & Garcia Co., August 2, 1927; 2863.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and Walter Chattaway, Jack Ridgeway & William Bantz, November 1, 1927; 2865.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and J. A. Curley, June 15, 1927; 2866.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and William H. Cochran, et ux, March 1, 1927; 2870.
  - John F. Casey Co. and Pittsburgh Coal Co., August 8, 1927; 2871.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and William Dobbins and Jesse J. Dobbins, January 19, 1927; 2875.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and The Dravo Contracting Co., January 27, 1928; 2878.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and The Dravo Contracting Co., July 22, 1927; 2879.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and A. E. Ford, et al, October 7, 1927; 2881.
  - Watson P. Davidson and Pittsburgh Coal Co. of Wisconsin, September 1, 1927; 2885.
  - New Pittsburgh Coal Co-Ohio and Tim Shay, eta al-Forest Run Coal Co, July 12, 1926-November 22, 1927; 2886.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and Emery Gates, October 7, 1927; 2887.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and Sygan Coal & Transfer Co.-Tullio and Gesbato Ghelarducci, August 29, 1927; 2888.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and Paul A. Witherspoon, October 31, 1927; 2889.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and Evan Jones, December 1, 1927; 2890.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and Robertson Coal & Coke Co., August 2, 1927; 2891.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and Ella Mining Co., March 11, 1927; 2893.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and Irwin Gas Coal Co., December 23, 1926; 2895.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and Adam E. Giehl & George J. Klein, October 10, 1927; 2900.
  - Irwin & Nelan and Pittsburgh Coal Co., August 8, 1927; 2904.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and The R. G. Johnson Co., July 22, 1927; 2905.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and George H. Crompton, et al, October 1, 1927; 2907.
  - William Joseph and Pittsburgh Coal Co., January 26, 1928; 2908.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and Sofie Kolosky, June 1, 1927; 2910.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and J. W. Kinney, July 2, 1927; 2911.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and Joseph K. Leader, November 1, 1926; 2918.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and S. C. Lovan, November 10, 1927; 2919.
  - Mc Kelvy-Hine Co. and Pittsburgh Coal Co., December 7, 1927; 2921.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and Mc Clane Mining Co., December 11, 1926-January 7, 1927; 2922.
  - Minter Homes Corporation and Pittsburgh Coal Co., November 21, 1927-February 24, 1928; 2926-1.
  - Minter Homes Corporation and Pittsburgh Coal Co., August 31, 1928-October 20, 1928; 2926-2.
  - Minter Homes Corporation and Pittsburgh Coal Co., October 24, 1928-August 15, 1929; 2926-3. (Box 70)
  - The Morrow Manufacturing Co. and Pittsburgh Coal Co., February 14-March 28, 1927; 2931.
  - J. C. Mc Bride and Peoples Natural Gas Co., January 19, 1922-July 3, 1925; 2932.
  - The Nicola Building Co. and Pittsburgh Coal Co., October 25, 1927; 2936.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and Polar Water Co., January 27, 1928-July 10, 1931; 2937.
  - Pitt Realty & Development Co. and Pittsburgh Coal Co., January 1, 1927; 2939.
  - Roberts and Schafer Co. and Pittsburgh Coal Co., April 8-July 15, 1927; 2950.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and S. M. Speers, July 8, 1927; 2952.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and Alex Solanik, April 6, 1928; 2953.
  - Harry Surgest and Pittsburgh Coal Co, November 16, 1927; 2954.
  - William Terry and Pittsburgh Coal Co., November 16, 1927; 2955.
  - Allen & Garcia Co. and Pittsburgh Coal Co., March 16, 1928; 2961.
  - Gannett, Seelye & Fleming Engineers, Inc., April 25, 1928; 2965.
  - A. G. Rothey, April 20, 1928-July 22, 1929; 2966-1.
  - A. G. Rothey, December 20, 1930-January 28, 1931; 2966-2.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and R. L. Trax, June 9, 1928; 2979.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and The Peoples Natural Gas Co., July 19, 1928; 2983.
  - The Koppers Coal Co. and Pittsburgh Coal Co., April 1, 1928; 2986.
  - The Dravo Contracting Co. and Pittsburgh Coal Co. (Blueprint pulled to map case 1/7/7-8), August 31, 1928; 2997.
  - Bishop Mc Cray and Pittsburgh Coal Co., November 20, 1928; 3029.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and John Balas, October 11, 1935; 3035.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and Duquesne Light Co., April 7, 1924-May 25, 1938; 3066.
  - H. F. Stark and Pittsburgh Coal Co., March 30, 1929; 3072.
  - Duquesne Light Co. and Pittsburgh Coal Co., April 27, 1929; 3082.
  - Duquesne Light Co. and Pittsburgh Coal Co., May 28, 1929; 3086.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and John H. Hamilton, July 3, 1929; 3100.
  - W. J. Shidler and Pittsburgh Coal Co., April 1, 1929; 3106.
  - The Enterprise Store Co. and The Great Lakes Power Co., 3111.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and Hillman Coal & Coke Co. (Blueprint pulled to map case 1/7/7-8), September 6, 1929; 3125.
  - The Guarantee Co. of North America, December 13, 1915-December 1, 1920; 3131-1.
  - The Guarantee Co. of North America, December 1, 1921-December 1, 1927; 3131-2.
  - The Guarantee Co. of North America, December 1, 1928-March 10, 1932; 3131-3.
  - The Guarantee Co. of North America, August 9, 1933; 3131-4. (Box 71)
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and County of Allegheny, September 27, 1929; 3133.
  - Schenley Fuel & Supply Co. and Pittsburgh Coal Co., December 2-12, 1929; 3136.
  - Davison Coke & Iron Co. (Pittsburgh Coke & Iron Co.) and Pittsburgh Coal Co., December 2, 1929-December 31, 1934; 3137.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and George A. Beaumont et ux, November 26, 1929; 3139.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and Robert L. Taylor, December 20, 1929-May 11, 1931; 3140.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and A. C. Stickel, November 26, 1929-April 1, 1930; 3141.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and W. C. McCallister et al (Courtney Coal Co.), November 1, 1929-June 8, 1943; 3142.
  - Carnegie Steel Co. and Pittsburgh Coal Co., January 1, 1930; 3143.
  - The Pittsburgh and Lake Erie Railroad Co. and Pittsburgh Coal Co., January 24, 1930-July 1, 1941; 3145.
  - New Pittsburgh Coal Co/Pittsburgh Coal Co. and Dan Shay, January 23, 1930; 3157.
  - J. B. Graves et ux and The Peoples Natural Gas Co., May 25, 1920-February 28, 1936; 3159.
  - The Bell Telephone Co. of Pennsylvania and Pittsburgh Coal Co., March 3, 1930-October 16, 1930; 3160.
  - New Pittsburgh Coal Co. and John D. Strickland & Henry S. Young (Liberty Coal Co.), June 26, 1924; 3161.
  - H. F. Stark and Pittsburgh Coal Co., March 24, 1930; 3166.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and Adam E. Giehl & George J. Klein, March 29, 1930-January 29, 1938; 3170.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and South Hills Coal Co., March 28, 1930-November 30, 1934; 3171.
  - William F. Tidball et ux, March 28, 1930; 3175.
  - Elsey River Transportation Line, Inc. and Pittsburgh Coal Co., March 15-July 10, 1930; 3176.
  - Elsey River Transportation Line, Inc. and Pittsburgh Coal Co., April 7, 1930; 3177.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and Martin Robeck et ux, May 9, 1930; 3182.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and H. F. Stark, June 16, 1930; 3186.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and George Wilson, December 29, 1931; 3187.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and Julia Rosko, May 28, 1930; 3192.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and The Bell Telephone Co. of Pennsylvania, June 20, 1930; 3193.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and P. J. Kirtley et ux, July 2, 1930-November 17, 1932; 3197.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and Frank Somoggi, July 2, 1930-October 26, 1934; 3198.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and Mark Schreiner, June 30, 1930; 3199.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and The Bell Telephone Co. of Pennsylvania, September 6, 1930-January 31, 1932; 3206.
  - Western Union Telegraph Co. and Pittsburgh Coal Co., August 21, 1930-September 30, 1933; 3207.
  - H. F. Stark and Pittsburgh Coal Co., November 10, 1930; 3225.
  - Hotels Statler Co., Inc. and Pittsburgh Coal Co., Inc., November 13, 1930; 3235.
  - J. B. Ford, Trustee and Pittsburgh Coal Co.-January 9, 1936; Union Guardian Trust Co.and Pittsburgh Coal Co. of Michigan-January 2, 1931, 3237.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and The Bell Telephone Co. of Pennsylvania, January 30, 1931-November 22, 1939; 3239.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and Walter R. Astfalk, October 9, 1930-July 28, 1937; 3241.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and Edwards McCrady Co., Jr., December 30, 1930; 3243.
  - Duquesne Light Co. and Pittsburgh Coal Co., November 1, 1930-September 30, 1933; 3247.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and Michael Supancic et ux, December 30, 1930; 3248.
  - W. J. Gowern and Pittsburgh Coal Co., March 4, 1931; 3252.
  - Hoffman Brothers Drilling Co. and Pittsburgh Coal Co., January 26, 1931; 3254.
  - West Penn Power Co. and Pittsburgh Coal Co., April 15, 1931; 3257.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and George Charlier et ux, April 24, 1931; 3264.
  - United States Coal & Supply Co., Inc., June 2, 1922-June 26, 1939; 3270.
  - W.J. Shidler and Pittsburgh Coal Co., June 8, 1931; 3273.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and A. J. Seabol, January 1, 1932-March 1, 1933; 3288.
  - The Bell Telephone Co. of Pennsylvania and Pittsburgh Coal Co., August 23, 1932-July 1, 1941; 3299.
  - West Penn Power Co. and Pittsburgh Coal Co., May 31, 1932; 3303. (Box 72)
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and The Bell Telephone Co. of Pennsylvania, June 1, 1932; 3304.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and Harry McDonald, October 26, 1932; 3309.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and The Bell Telephone Co. of Pennsylvania, August 31, 1932; 3310.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and Raymond Vaia, November 11, 1932-November 11, 1937; 3314.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and The Bell Telephone Co. of Pennsylvania, November 30, 1932; 3318.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and The Bell Telephone Co. of Pennsylvania, November 30, 1932-November 22, 1939; 3319.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and Westmoreland Coal Co., October 1, 1932; 3321.
  - William Windsheimer et ux and Pittsburgh Coal Co., December 31, 1932-December 31, 1937; 3322.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and A. C. Smith, November 22, 1932; 3326.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and Alva Snyder, March 1, 1933-December 31, 1937; 3331.
  - W. J. Rainey, Inc. and Pittsburgh Coal Co., March 29, 1933; 3332.
  - South Hills Coal Co. and Pittsburgh Coal Co., November 3, 1927-July 31, 1933; 3340.
  - The R. G. Johnson Co. and Pittsburgh Coal Co., December 28, 1933; 3341.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and Walter N. Ridgeway, January 5, 1934-January 18, 1935; 3342.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co.-John N. Sposato, December 19, 1933-November 26, 1937; 3343.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and Alphonse Giovannelli, January 1, 1934; 3344.
  - The Bell Telephone Co. of Pennsylvania and Pittsburgh Coal Co., August 1, 1933-July 1, 1941; 3350.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and Civil Works Administration, January 12-29, 1934; 3355.
  - County of Washington and Pittsburgh Coal Co., January 18, 1934; 3357.
  - John Wanamaker Philadelphia and Pittsburgh Coal Co., January 31, 1934; 3360.
  - Baltimore Realty Trust, Inc. and Pittsburgh Coal Co., May 31, 1934; 3362.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and Staney Anglcyk, April 6, 1934; 3367.
  - William Semple Ferry Co., January 2, 1913-July 18, 1940; 3372.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and William Semple Ferry Co., July 18, 1940; 3373.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and The Haydite Co., Inc., June 25, 1934-October 31, 1937; 3376.
  - Duquesne Light Co. and Pittsburgh Coal Co., July 16, 1934; 3378.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and William B. Redd, July 26, 1934; 3379.
  - Pihl & Miller and Pittsburgh Coal Co., September 21, 1934; 3383.
  - A. G. Rothey and Pittsburgh Coal Co., January 9, 1935; 3399.
  - Mary Fuller Frazier et al Executors of the estate of Alice K. Fuller and Pittsburgh Coal Co., December 12, 1934; 3402.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and Duquense Light Co., January 18, 1935; 3404.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and William Arbaugh, February 8, 1935; 3407.
  - Debenture Bonds/Lost Coupons, August 1, 1934; 3408.
  - H. Lee Mason, Jr. by Feltyberger Bros, Agents and Pittsburgh Coal Co., March 7, 1935; 3414.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and Glenn C. Reiter, February 1, 1935; 3415.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and Mell J. Williams, January 1, 1935; 3421.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and Ralph Holzhauser, February 1, 1935; 3427.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and Emery Gates, August 15, 1935-October 31, 1942; 3432.
  - The Monongahela River Consolidated Coal & Coke Co. and Pittsburgh-Westmoreland Coal Co., August 13, 1907; 3438.
  - The Dravo Contracting Co and Sundry Contracts, August 23, 1935-November 14, 1935; 3440.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and Joseph J. Morosini et ux, August 26, 1935; 3441.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and Whitely Creek Coal Co. and Stany Anglcyk, April 12, 1935; 3443.
  - Edward W. Beedle et al and Pittsburgh Coal Co., October 13, 1942; 3445.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and John F. Washabaugh and James L. Woodruff, October 15, 1935-July 6, 1936; 3448.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and Norwood P. Johnston, February 5, 1936; 3463.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and George Love, June 23, 1936; 3478.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and Burke Coal Co., January 14-May 24, 1937; 3485.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and Whiteley Creek Coal Co. and Stany Anglcyk, August 12, 1936; 3492.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and J. M. Morrison, August 12, 1936; 3493.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and S. M. Speers, August 13, 1936; 3496.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and George McDonald, Jr., September 4, 1936; 3503.
  - Jay W. Johns and Pittsburgh Coal Co., October 16, 1936; 3513.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and Clifford I. Taylor, November 6, 1936; 3519.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and Henry Fleming, December 31, 1936; 3528. (Box 73)
  - Swen G. Selen and Pittsburgh Coal Co., December 28, 1936; 3529.
  - Great Lakes Dredge & Dock Co. and Pittsburgh Coal Co., February 5, 1937; 3530.
  - National Shipping Co. and Pittsburgh Coal Co., March 5, 1937-November 1, 1940; 3541.
  - The Pennsylvania Railroad Co. and Pittsburgh Coal Co., February 23, 1937; 3545.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and Joseph Andrewsky et ux, May 28, 1937; 3562.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and Floyd A. Kirkland & Edward R. Koch, July 12, 1943; 3564.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and Montour Collieries Co., August 30, 1937-April 30, 1942; 3579.
  - Pihl & Miller, Inc., September 27, 1937; 3588.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and H. N. Hough & T. R. Arthur, September 27, 1937; 3590.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and John Coletti et ux, November 22, 1937; 3599.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and Amos Hamilton et ux, October 1, 1937; 3603.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and Julia Statzula, December 29, 1937; 3615.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and Oliver C. Leeper, December 29, 1937; 3617.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and Charles E. Campbell, January 17, 1938; 3627.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and Frank Remic, Jr., February 1, 1938-March 1, 1941; 3628.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and Forrest E. Forsythe, March 11, 1938; 3639.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and A. B. Coleman, March 29, 1938; 3642.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and Mike Clickovich and Miller Savage, March 1, 1938; 3657.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and Samuel N. Sethman & Guffey G. Finley, May 6, 1938-August 31, 1942; 3658.
  - New Pittsburgh Coal Co. and Clifford Jacobs & William Davis, June 2, 1938-March 1, 1942; 3664.
  - The Pennsylvania Railroad Co. and Pittsburgh Coal Co., May 18, 1938; 3668.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and Charles E. Riley, Robert K. Scott and Charles Agrippa, July 15, 1938-March 31, 1944; 3684.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and Mike Demitroff, June 17, 1938-July 1, 1939; 3686.
  - West Penn Power Co. and Pittsburgh Coal Co., July 14, 1938; 3687.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and Robert Capri and M. W. Fresa, August 26, 1938; 3702.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and R. E. Clark, September 29, 1938; 3716.
  - New Pittsburgh Coal Co. and Michael Bentz, October 31, 1938-August 1, 1941; 3727.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and Campbell Transportation Co., September 17, 1938; 3737.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and Union Barge Line, October 6-25, 1938; 3738.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and Sam Bertone, February 17, 1939-September 30, 1940; 3747.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and William F. Beatty, June 7, 1943-March 31, 1944; 3748.
  - O. C. Cluss Lumber Co. and Pittsburgh Coal Co., February 11, 1939; 3749.
  - Ross G. Menoher and Pittsburgh Coal Co., July 11, 1941; 3754.
  - A. E. & E. W. Brown and Pittsburgh Coal Co., April 1, 1939; 3767. (Box 74)
  - Frank B. Oles et ux and Pittsburgh Coal Co., August 28, 1939; 3815.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and Homer L. Nixon, October 26, 1939; 3832.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and Bartlo Sacco, October 26, 1939; 3833.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and The Pittsburgh, Lisbon & Western Railroad Co., January 1, 1942; 3837.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and Knowles Martin, November 27, 1939-May 27, 1940; 3842.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and Louis Dines, December 4, 1939-November 30, 1941; 3843.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and Frank Prah & Frank Oberlitner, September 24, 1943; 3904.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and Louis Hahn & Son, July 8, 1940; 3929.
  - McCrady Construction Co. and Pittsburgh Coal Co., August 19, 1940; 3930.
  - Duquesne Light Co. and Pittsburgh Coal Co., August 8, 1940-July 1, 1941; 3945.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and The Bell Telephone Co. of Pennsylvania, September 23, 1940; 3948.
  - The Bell Telephone Co. of Pennsylvania and Pittsburgh Coal Co., October 14, 1940-July 1, 1941; 3949.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and The Bell Telephone Co. of Pennsylvania, October 22, 1940; 3967.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and Nickolas P. Sasso, December 9, 1940; 3971.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and Stanley Toy, December 16, 1940; 3972.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and W. R. Konkle, September 9, 1943; 3980.
  - Jay C. Speaker and Pittsburgh Coal Co., December 26, 1940; 3989.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and Robert McFarlane & George C. Kuehnert, October 13, 1943; 3991.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and Fred H. Phillips, January 22, 1941; 3995.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and The Chesapeake & Ohio Railway Co., October 11, 1940; 4000.
  - Groomes Construction Co. and Pittsburgh Coal Co. (Blueprint pulled to map case 1/7/7-8), March 4, 1941; 4001.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and John M. G. Brown et al, June 16, 1941; 4029.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and Skeloski, Stanley J. & Ulish, Walter H., August 18, 1941; 4055.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and Thomas H. Queen, April 25, 1944; 4074.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and Fred Lilhol, Jr., December 23, 1943; 4087.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and Joseph Baucant, February 11, 1944; 4090.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and John W. Wray, February 14, 1944; 4097.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and William L. Piccolomini, December 12, 1941; 4116.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and Robert Mac Farlane, December 1, 1943; 4129.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and Rothey Bros., Inc., January 29, 1942; 4131.